How are we feeling about the run today, boys?
Tindalos?
Mascerville?
Oh, is that so?
Yeah, good job, boys.
It's been a few months since I arrived in Rosenberg.
I've been working with different parties as a mercenary.
Helping out on their jobs and trying to build a good reputation among the townsfolk and adventurers.
The idea is to get popular enough that word about me reaches Zenith, wherever she is.
Okay, only like a hundred left to go.
Come on, Heracles!
Hulk!
Listen up!
Step Leader has taken this S-ranked extermination job.
We'll clear the Snowdrake infestation out of Ilbrun Cave in no time.
And we'll set out immediately!
Yeah!
Hope the rest of you are ready to marvel at our greatness when we return.
Hey, Quagmire, thanks again for the other day.
Oh no, I should be thanking you.
We're leaving town today, Quagmire.
But I'll be sure to send word if I hear anything about your mother out there, alright?
Oh, thank you.
Please do.
Looks like all my hard work is starting to pay off.
Because Rudeus Greyrat now has quite the reputation in this town.
I'll take this one.
Although more people do know me by my nickname, Quagmire, than my real one.
Making a name for yourself in one town takes a few months to a year.
It feels like a hell of a long time, but right now, it's the best plan I have.
Isn't that right, Master Roxy?
I'm Rudeus Greyrat.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
You that famous Quagmire guy?
I don't know if I'm all that famous, but yes.
Well then, get to work, celebrity.
Yes, sir.
Bye.
So I'm going to do it again
I feel like I'm going to go
That time I'm going to go
Where am I going?
I'm going to go
I'm not going to go
You are dying
Oh, that is
Good boys, way to go.
On your way home?
Yes. I just finished a job, so I'll report it and head back to the inn.
Well, we were just about to pick out a new job ourselves. You want to join us?
Yeah, I...
I met Counter Arrow as soon as I got here, and I've worked with them a lot since.
Teaming up with one party over and over doesn't do much for my goal, but it's hard to turn them down.
Uh, when would you guys be heading out?
Oh my god, if you're not interested, then just say no. It's not like we're desperate.
Sorry about that. I'm just indecisive.
You're sorry about everything. It's kind of pathetic.
Sarah, that's enough.
Whatever. So, what you think? You coming?
I am. I appreciate the invite.
Well then, let's get in there and find a job, shall we?
The Galga ruins were originally built as a fortress during the first human-demon war.
Wow.
I saw some pretty cool structures on the demon continent, but nothing quite like this.
Don't just stand there staring.
Oh, sorry. I'm coming.
Do you like architecture?
Not especially. I just haven't seen many places this impressive before, you know?
Here.
Hey, watch your hands, Kree.
I thought I was.
Sorry about that.
This must be the place.
Oh.
All we're here to do is collect a bunch of these fancy scales, and they're just lying around everywhere.
Pretty easy for an A-class job.
This is still Snowdrake territory, so stay alert. Don't go past that statue.
Got it.
Actually, fighting the Snowdrakes would suck, but they only use this passage to get from place to place, so we can just hide if any of them show up, but...
It's a little too quiet.
You know, that buxom babe statue kind of reminds me of...
Talk about taking artistic license.
What was that?
I've got a bad feeling about this.
We're under attack!
What?
Why does this keep happening?
Guys?
What?
May the smoldering spark call for the great and searing blessing, Blamethrower!
Let's go, Patrice!
On it!
These things aren't after us. Just hit the ones charging towards us and knock them off course.
Gotcha!
Coming in from the left!
Don't just stand around! You're in this fight too, moron!
Right!
Haven't we had enough?
Alright, let's press the attack as well.
Thought you'd never ask!
Is it over?
Hey there! I'm Timothy of Counter Arrow. Thank you!
You got a lot of nerve giving me that dopey smile after you try to swipe our prey.
Are you joking? We didn't know anyone else was working a job down here.
I announced it in front of the entire guild!
Well, it's news to us!
Do you know something about this, Rudeus?
Well, come to think of it, he did mention something about a job at the guild hall the other day.
I think they were going to exterminate a Snowdrake infestation in Ilbrun Cave.
In Ilbrun Cave! That's a day and a half away from here! These are the Galga ruins!
Suzanne, please, it's fine.
You okay, Timothy? How's your face feeling?
I'm fine. He was kind enough to take it easy on me.
Sarah, lower your bow, please.
I think I see what happened.
This castle was once the base for a demon king, with tunnels branching off to who knows where.
Maybe one of them opened up between the ruins and the cave.
So what? You're saying you came out here on a different job?
That's right. You can confirm this with the guild when you return to town, if you like.
Well, sorry for punching you out of nowhere, then.
That's all right. We both misunderstood the situation. I'm sorry we had to run into each other.
Well, I don't care how many you killed. These drakes were still our prey.
We'll let you claim one quarts, but that's it. You understand me?
Yes, of course.
Okay, then. Let's gather up our scales and head on back to town. We can celebrate together once we get there.
You got it, boss. I need a drink after this.
Hey, Rudeus. You should come to the after party for once.
Huh?
Well then.
Cheers!
Feels good to have made it out of that mess without losing anyone, though it was pretty close for a minute there.
Yeah, you got really lucky, Rudeus.
Was that luck? Felt more like you guys rescued me.
Yeah, and you're lucky that we did. Most parties would have left you to die out there.
Well, I'm grateful.
Don't thank me.
You should be thanking Timothy and Suzanne. They deserve all the credit.
Oh, you say that now, but you're the one who rushed back in before any of us.
You insisted that we could save him.
Shut up, Suzanne!
You helped us out last time with the Grizzlies, so I wanted to return the favor.
I don't like being in anyone's debt, and that's all there is to it.
In any case, we made it back in one piece.
And got plenty of cash.
That's my kind of job.
Although, shame we had to run into that jerk.
Would have been even better if we hadn't.
Yeah, being the toughest party in the guild made them pretty insufferable.
I wish they'd stick to their damn labyrinths.
And that jackass calls himself a party leader.
I can't help but wonder if Paul was like that when he was younger.
What do you want?
I was all worked up back in the cave, so I thought I'd come set things straight with you people.
I didn't know what was going on, and I kinda screwed up.
So guess what I'm trying to say?
That was my bad or whatever.
With that said, her face just pisses me off, man.
Always grinning like an idiot, and then you just let a guy punch you like that?
Didn't even argue or nothing.
You're just all smiles and bruises, and I hate that shit.
Sometimes a man's gotta fight, you feel me?
Well, yes, perhaps you're right.
Suzanne often tells me I'm too passive.
I'll remember that.
Good, yeah, you remember that.
Now, Quagmire.
Yes?
Timmy hears one thing, but I can't stand your ass, kid.
You got this weird people-pleasing attitude, but no one's buying it.
Yeah, and that creepy grin of yours makes me sick.
Maybe you think that's a smile, but it ain't.
Try a little harder.
We can see the contempt in your eyes.
Who do you think you are, huh?
Come on, let go of me.
Give it a rest, all right?
Look at him!
This dumb-faced, pouty-crymouth.
You're the saddest boy in the world.
I don't know what happened to you, Quagmire, but you're depressing.
So you can either learn to man up and face your stupid problems,
or get the hell out of my guild!
I didn't realize I bothered you so much.
I'll do my best to stay out of your sight from now on.
Oh, bullshit!
What is that supposed to mean?
Are you trying to piss me off?!
Is it fun for you acting like a martyr all the time,
or acting like you're too good for money?
We all need cash to survive, you brat!
That's enough, soul. Go sleep this off.
Shut up!
Let me go, Conrad.
Hey, listen, Quagmire.
If you hate your life so much, drop dead!
At least then I won't have to see your stupid face again
until I'm sick of your shit!
Ugh, that guy is the worst.
Oh, waiting for cheap jobs again?
I have my reasons for doing this.
Well, I bet your reasons suck.
You half-ass everything you ever do, don't you?
I have my own idea.
Hello.
Oh, it's Rudeus.
Is something wrong?
It's Mimir and Sarah.
Are they okay?
They're both dead.
Oh.
I...
No. Mimir is dead, but Sarah just got separated.
If we leave now, we may still be able to find her.
If we try to go back out right now in this blizzard, we'll die long before we ever find her.
We shouldn't have left. I shouldn't have made the call.
We all agreed to run. We're equally responsible, okay?
Um, where did you lose her?
In Trier Forest, to the west.
The blizzard blinded us, and then a herd of snow buffalo attacked.
I see. That must have been awful. But I should be going.
Well, I bet your reasons suck. You half-ass everything you ever do, don't you?
Well, I bet your reasons suck.
You half-ass everything you ever do, don't you?
Maybe he was right. What the hell am I doing out here alone?
Stroking my own ego?
Of course I want to find Sarah, but I don't think I even care if she's alive or dead.
Maybe I just want to take action and have something to show for it.
Get a result, any result.
Or maybe I wanted to actively make the choice not to abandon someone.
The way Eris abandoned me.
That could be all there is to it.
But what if I do find her?
I don't know. Maybe I shouldn't get my hopes up.
I'm not going to accomplish anything here.
How could I?
Is that Mimir?
Where is Sarah?
It's not like Sarah and I were close or anything, but she hadn't been nearly as prickly lately.
I bet we could have been friends eventually.
Sarah!
Who's there?
It's Rudeus.
Rudeus?
I'm here to save you.
Okay, now, do you mind?
Nope, go ahead.
Thank you very much.
What are you thanking me for, weirdo?
There's nothing wrong with your legs still, is there?
Mm-mm.
It's fine.
It doesn't even hurt now.
All good.
Well, if you're sure.
I just feel like something is off.
I told you, everything is fine.
Oh, but you being here alone is kind of weird, I guess.
Uh, well, you know, your party mentioned you were missing, so...
What?
Are they all okay?
Amir is dead.
Oh.
You ready to head back to town?
Mm-hmm.
Listen!
Hm.
I'm really glad you came to rescue me.
And just like that, something inside me clicked together.
I feel like I've been forgiven for everything I've done and been.
In a way, I sort of feel like Sarah just saved me.
Suzanne!
Sarah!
You had me so worried.
We were just setting out to go look for you again.
It's okay.
Rudeus rescued me.
Did you...
Did you set out by yourself after we told you what happened last night?
Well, I...
Yeah.
Do you have any idea how reckless that was?
How would we have felt if you had died out there?
Suzanne!
You don't have to put it like that.
Jeez!
No, I suppose you're right about that.
I'm not exactly myself right now.
Rudeus?
I apologize.
I should have started by saying thank you for saving her.
Sorry.
Rudeus.
I'm grateful.
I mean that with all I am.
If there's any way at all we can repay you, just name it.
Please, you don't need to thank me.
You've done so much to help me already.
Honest.
And I mean it too.
Counter Arrow has been there for me since the second we stepped foot in this town.
They don't owe me a thing.
If you like, we can just say this makes us even, okay?
Really?
If you insist.
But if you need us, we'll always be around.
Okay.
And hey, the same goes for you guys.
I ought to go home.
Okay, I'll walk you there.
Rudeus!
If you like, we can just say this makes us even, okay?
Really?
If you insist.
But if you need us, we'll always be around.
Okay.
And hey, the same goes for you guys.
I ought to go home.
Okay.
I'll walk you there.
Rudeus!
Rudeus, I'll see you later.
Make sure you get some rest today.
Time for a break.
I think I earned it.
I feel like I can sleep soundly for the first time in ages.